Sentence,Label
Alice and Bob live in the USA,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', '0', '0', 'COUNTRY']"
Charlie visited Paris in France,"['PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY']"
Emily works at Google in California,"['PERSON', '0', '0', 'ORG', '0', 'STATE']"
James met Laura in London,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY']"
Sarah and John are friends,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', '0']"
Microsoft is a major company in the USA,"['ORG', '0', '0', '0', '0', '0', '0', 'COUNTRY']"
The Eiffel Tower is in Paris,"['0', 'LOCATION', 'LOCATION', '0', '0', 'CITY']"
Canada is a country in America,"['COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', '0', 'CONTINENT']"
Anna is from Germany,"['PERSON', '0', '0', 'COUNTRY']"
Toyota is headquartered in Japan,"['ORG', '0', '0', '0', 'COUNTRY']"
Google and Facebook are competitors,"['ORG', '0', 'ORG', '0', '0']"
Alice and Bob visited Paris in France and met with Google,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
Bob and Charlie visited London in UK and met with Microsoft,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
Charlie and David visited Tokyo in Japan and met with Apple,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
David and Eve visited Seattle in USA and met with Amazon,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
Eve and Frank visited Berlin in Germany and met with Tesla,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
Frank and Grace visited Madrid in Spain and met with Facebook,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
Grace and Hank visited Rome in Italy and met with Intel,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
Hank and Ivy visited Sydney in Australia and met with IBM,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
Ivy and Jack visited Warsaw in Poland and met with Netflix,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
Jack and Karen visited Cairo in Egypt and met with Samsung,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
Karen and Alice visited Paris in France and met with Google,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
Alice and Bob visited London in UK and met with Microsoft,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
Bob and Charlie visited Tokyo in Japan and met with Apple,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
Charlie and David visited Seattle in USA and met with Amazon,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
David and Eve visited Berlin in Germany and met with Tesla,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
Eve and Frank visited Madrid in Spain and met with Facebook,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
Frank and Grace visited Rome in Italy and met with Intel,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
Grace and Hank visited Sydney in Australia and met with IBM,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
Hank and Ivy visited Warsaw in Poland and met with Netflix,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
Ivy and Jack visited Cairo in Egypt and met with Samsung,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
Jack and Karen visited Paris in France and met with Google,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
Karen and Alice visited London in UK and met with Microsoft,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
Alice and Bob visited Tokyo in Japan and met with Apple,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
Bob and Charlie visited Seattle in USA and met with Amazon,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
Charlie and David visited Berlin in Germany and met with Tesla,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
David and Eve visited Madrid in Spain and met with Facebook,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
Eve and Frank visited Rome in Italy and met with Intel,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
Frank and Grace visited Sydney in Australia and met with IBM,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
Grace and Hank visited Warsaw in Poland and met with Netflix,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
Hank and Ivy visited Cairo in Egypt and met with Samsung,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
Ivy and Jack visited Paris in France and met with Google,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
Jack and Karen visited London in UK and met with Microsoft,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
Karen and Alice visited Tokyo in Japan and met with Apple,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
Alice and Bob visited Seattle in USA and met with Amazon,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
Bob and Charlie visited Berlin in Germany and met with Tesla,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
Charlie and David visited Madrid in Spain and met with Facebook,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
David and Eve visited Rome in Italy and met with Intel,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
Eve and Frank visited Sydney in Australia and met with IBM,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
Frank and Grace visited Warsaw in Poland and met with Netflix,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
Grace and Hank visited Cairo in Egypt and met with Samsung,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
Hank and Ivy visited Paris in France and met with Google,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
Ivy and Jack visited London in UK and met with Microsoft,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
Jack and Karen visited Tokyo in Japan and met with Apple,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
Karen and Alice visited Seattle in USA and met with Amazon,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
Alice and Bob visited Berlin in Germany and met with Tesla,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
Bob and Charlie visited Madrid in Spain and met with Facebook,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
Charlie and David visited Rome in Italy and met with Intel,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
David and Eve visited Sydney in Australia and met with IBM,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
Eve and Frank visited Warsaw in Poland and met with Netflix,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
Frank and Grace visited Cairo in Egypt and met with Samsung,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
Grace and Hank visited Paris in France and met with Google,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
Hank and Ivy visited London in UK and met with Microsoft,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
Ivy and Jack visited Tokyo in Japan and met with Apple,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
Jack and Karen visited Seattle in USA and met with Amazon,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
Karen and Alice visited Berlin in Germany and met with Tesla,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
Alice and Bob visited Madrid in Spain and met with Facebook,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
Bob and Charlie visited Rome in Italy and met with Intel,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
Charlie and David visited Sydney in Australia and met with IBM,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
David and Eve visited Warsaw in Poland and met with Netflix,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
Eve and Frank visited Cairo in Egypt and met with Samsung,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
Frank and Grace visited Paris in France and met with Google,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
Grace and Hank visited London in UK and met with Microsoft,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
Hank and Ivy visited Tokyo in Japan and met with Apple,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
Ivy and Jack visited Seattle in USA and met with Amazon,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
Jack and Karen visited Berlin in Germany and met with Tesla,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
Karen and Alice visited Madrid in Spain and met with Facebook,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
Alice and Bob visited Rome in Italy and met with Intel,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
Bob and Charlie visited Sydney in Australia and met with IBM,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
Charlie and David visited Warsaw in Poland and met with Netflix,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
David and Eve visited Cairo in Egypt and met with Samsung,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
Eve and Frank visited Paris in France and met with Google,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
Frank and Grace visited London in UK and met with Microsoft,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
Grace and Hank visited Tokyo in Japan and met with Apple,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
Hank and Ivy visited Seattle in USA and met with Amazon,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
Ivy and Jack visited Berlin in Germany and met with Tesla,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
Jack and Karen visited Madrid in Spain and met with Facebook,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
Karen and Alice visited Rome in Italy and met with Intel,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
Alice and Bob visited Sydney in Australia and met with IBM,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
Bob and Charlie visited Warsaw in Poland and met with Netflix,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
Charlie and David visited Cairo in Egypt and met with Samsung,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
David and Eve visited Paris in France and met with Google,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
Eve and Frank visited London in UK and met with Microsoft,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
Frank and Grace visited Tokyo in Japan and met with Apple,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
Grace and Hank visited Seattle in USA and met with Amazon,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
Hank and Ivy visited Berlin in Germany and met with Tesla,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
Ivy and Jack visited Madrid in Spain and met with Facebook,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
Jack and Karen visited Rome in Italy and met with Intel,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
Karen and Alice visited Sydney in Australia and met with IBM,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"
Alice and Bob visited Warsaw in Poland and met with Netflix,"['PERSON', '0', 'PERSON', '0', 'CITY', '0', 'COUNTRY', '0', '0', '0', 'ORG']"